https://www.fiorano.com/company/privacy

Featured Blogs
Fiorano to Deliver Next Generation Banking Technology on IBM LinuxONE
Sales Enquiries
send us a few details and we will get back.
Fiorano Privacy Policy
Fiorano Software, Inc. and its Affiliates (collectively, "Fiorano") are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.
Fiorano has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
Personal Information
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an e-mail address, phone number, or other contact information, whether at work or at home.
In general, you can visit Fiorano's web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the web, we may transfer that Information, within Fiorano or to Fiorano's third party service providers, partners or resellers, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Fiorano strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy.
We periodically update this Privacy Policy. If you subscribe to our Subscription Service, then you will receive notice when this Privacy Policy is modified. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. By using our website, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our website or platform(s).
Information we collect
Cookies and Other Navigation Tracking Technologies
Navigational Information: Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other navigation tracking technology. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and related technology may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a web user.
Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and / or password to gain access to certain parts of the Fiorano website.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site and your web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
Notice
Where Fiorano collects Personal Information online, we intend to post a purpose statement that explains why Personal Information will be collected and whether we plan to share such Personal Information outside of Fiorano or those working on Fiorano's behalf. We do not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Fiorano's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.
Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Fiorano. The notices we intend to provide where Fiorano collects Personal Information on the web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of Fiorano's web sites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services that involve our interaction with you. If you chose to have a relationship with Fiorano, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.
In general we will keep your data as long as a business relationship exists with the Enterprise or you or the Organization you work for has use of our products or have expressed interest in our products, technology or services or who we believe might have use for our products/technologies in the future, and consent has not been withdrawn. This may include information after you have left a specific organization in order to preserve communication relating to products, solutions and services regarding which we may for legitimate business interests keep on our records
Information about Children
Our website is not intended for children. If you believe that we have collected information about children under your care who are under 13 years of age, please contact privacy@fiorano.com so we may delete the information.
How we use information we collect
Compliance with our Privacy Policy
We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who subscribe to our services or newsletters are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy
Commitment
We are committed to maintaining privacy and will support current industry initiatives to preserve
individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy on-line is an evolving area, and Fiorano's
web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our
Online Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@fiorano.com
We never sell or distribute Personal Information
We will never sell Personal Information we collect to any third party.
Use of Personal Information
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to: (a) improve your browsing experience by personalizing our website; (b) send information to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means, and (c) send you marketing communications relating to our business. We may, from time to time, contact you regarding a particular offering that may be of interest to you.
Use of Navigational Information
We may use Navigational Information to operate and improve our website. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about Fiorano.
Customer Testimonials and Comments
We occasionally post customer testimonials and comments on our Websites, which may contain Personal Information. In such cases we obtain each customer's consent via email prior to posting any testimonials.
Security of your Personal Information
We use a variety of security protocols and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on our servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When sensitive Personal Information is collected on our Websites and/or transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as SSL.
Access / Accuracy
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Fiorano wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. We may periodically send out communication to check the accuracy of the information we hold about you. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Fiorano should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information via Email to us, at privacy@Fiorano.com. You may also instruct us to erase all personally identifiable information about you on our records.
Third Party Services
Third parties provide certain services on Fiorano's behalf. Fiorano may provide information, including Personal Information that you have provided to Fiorano or that Fiorano collects about you through social media identifiers such as LinkedIn or Twitter, to third party service providers, including partners and resellers, to help us deliver programs, products, information and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Fiorano maintains its web site and mailing lists. Fiorano will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Fiorano's behalf. Fiorano does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Fiorano's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.
Your Consent
By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Fiorano's processing of Personal Information for the purposes detailed above as well as those explained where Fiorano collects Personal Information on the web. Each time you provide personally identifiable data you will be informed on the form or link regarding data that we will record and will be given an opportunity to provide your Consent or withhold it.
Legitimate Interests
Under the General Data Protection Regulation certain categories of personal data processed by Fiorano falls under ‘legitimate interests’. Fiorano occasionally may reach out to business to business contacts for marketing related data processing under such a Legitimate Interests category based on the following assessments:
Purpose test: Fiorano as a commercial entity has a legitimate interest in promoting its products and services and also to occasionally publish related offers to business contacts, which it may do through direct marketing.
Necessity test: Fiorano may, in cases where assessments have demonstrated that direct marketing is the most effective manner, follow email and other forms of marketing to promote its business. In such cases this processing will be solely restricted to the processing of Business-to-Business (B2B) contacts. Fiorano will not use direct marketing with non-B2B contacts.
Balancing test: Fiorano will only use direct marketing for occasional business-to-business marketing, to business personnel with decision making / influencing / budgetary responsibilities in a business context who we believe in their roles will reasonably expect to be contacted with marketing material relating to his / her professional role.
In all cases, while we do not anticipate any of our direct marketing to be objectionable, recipients will always have the option to unsubscribe from updates in which case once such communication has been received, Fiorano will move related records to a restricted Do Not Contact database. In no manner and at any point will Fiorano engage in direct marketing activities that does not comply with the Purpose, Necessity and Balancing purposes outlined above, or will Fiorano engage in processing activities that we believe may override the rights of Data Subjects. We also do not sell your information to any other parties.
Your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation:
Under the EUs GDPR laws, you have the following general rights as a data subject:
Access:
the right to request information about how we process your Personal Information and also to obtain a copy of that Personal Information.
Rectification:
the right to request the rectification of inaccurate Personal Information about you and for any incomplete Personal Information about you to be completed.
Objection:
the right to object to the processing of your Personal Information, which is based on our legitimate interests (as described above).
Erasure: the right to request the erasure of your Personal Information (subject to certain conditions).
Automated decision-making:
the right not to have a decision made about you that is based solely on automated processing
Restriction:
the right to ask us to restrict our processing of your Personal Information.
Portability: the right to receive your Personal Information as per our records in a machine readable format free of charge. You may direct us to provide this data to a third party which we will do as is technologically reasonable.
In addition to the above, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your Personal Information infringes applicable data protection law.
Please feel free to direct any questions, comments, or complaints regarding this privacy statement or the privacy practices of Fiorano Software to our Data Protection Officer:
Fiorano Software Limited
Attention: Data Protection Officer
3000 Hillswood Drive, Hillswood Business Park
Chertsey, Surrey KT16 0RS
Phone : +44 (0) 1932895005
Email: privacy@fiorano.com
Fiorano Privacy Policy
Fiorano Software, Inc. and its Affiliates (collectively, "Fiorano") are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.
Fiorano has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
Personal Information
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an e-mail address, phone number, or other contact information, whether at work or at home.
In general, you can visit Fiorano's web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the web, we may transfer that Information, within Fiorano or to Fiorano's third party service providers, partners or resellers, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Fiorano strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy.
We periodically update this Privacy Policy. If you subscribe to our Subscription Service, then you will receive notice when this Privacy Policy is modified. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. By using our website, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our website or platform(s).
Information we collect
Cookies and Other Navigation Tracking Technologies
Navigational Information: Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other navigation tracking technology. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and related technology may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a web user.
Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and / or password to gain access to certain parts of the Fiorano website.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site and your web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
Notice
Where Fiorano collects Personal Information online, we intend to post a purpose statement that explains why Personal Information will be collected and whether we plan to share such Personal Information outside of Fiorano or those working on Fiorano's behalf. We do not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Fiorano's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.
Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Fiorano. The notices we intend to provide where Fiorano collects Personal Information on the web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of Fiorano's web sites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services that involve our interaction with you. If you chose to have a relationship with Fiorano, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.
In general we will keep your data as long as a business relationship exists with the Enterprise or you or the Organization you work for has use of our products or have expressed interest in our products, technology or services or who we believe might have use for our products/technologies in the future, and consent has not been withdrawn. This may include information after you have left a specific organization in order to preserve communication relating to products, solutions and services regarding which we may for legitimate business interests keep on our records
Information about Children
Our website is not intended for children. If you believe that we have collected information about children under your care who are under 13 years of age, please contact privacy@fiorano.com so we may delete the information.
How we use information we collect
Compliance with our Privacy Policy
We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who subscribe to our services or newsletters are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy
Commitment
We are committed to maintaining privacy and will support current industry initiatives to preserve
individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy on-line is an evolving area, and Fiorano's
web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our
Online Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@fiorano.com
We never sell or distribute Personal Information
We will never sell Personal Information we collect to any third party.
Use of Personal Information
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to: (a) improve your browsing experience by personalizing our website; (b) send information to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means, and (c) send you marketing communications relating to our business. We may, from time to time, contact you regarding a particular offering that may be of interest to you.
Use of Navigational Information
We may use Navigational Information to operate and improve our website. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about Fiorano.
Customer Testimonials and Comments
We occasionally post customer testimonials and comments on our Websites, which may contain Personal Information. In such cases we obtain each customer's consent via email prior to posting any testimonials.
Security of your Personal Information
We use a variety of security protocols and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on our servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When sensitive Personal Information is collected on our Websites and/or transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as SSL.
Access / Accuracy
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Fiorano wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. We may periodically send out communication to check the accuracy of the information we hold about you. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Fiorano should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information via Email to us, at privacy@fiorano.com. You may also instruct us to erase all personally identifiable information about you on our records.
Third Party Services
Third parties provide certain services on Fiorano's behalf. Fiorano may provide information, including Personal Information that you have provided to Fiorano or that Fiorano collects about you through social media identifiers such as LinkedIn or Twitter, to third party service providers, including partners and resellers, to help us deliver programs, products, information and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Fiorano maintains its web site and mailing lists. Fiorano will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Fiorano's behalf. Fiorano does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Fiorano's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.
Your Consent
By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Fiorano's processing of Personal Information for the purposes detailed above as well as those explained where Fiorano collects Personal Information on the web. Each time you provide personally identifiable data you will be informed on the form or link regarding data that we will record and will be given an opportunity to provide your Consent or withhold it.
Legitimate Interests
Under the General Data Protection Regulation certain categories of personal data processed by Fiorano falls under ‘legitimate interests’. Fiorano occasionally may reach out to business to business contacts for marketing related data processing under such a Legitimate Interests category based on the following assessments:
Purpose test: Fiorano as a commercial entity has a legitimate interest in promoting its products and services and also to occasionally publish related offers to business contacts, which it may do through direct marketing.
Necessity test: Fiorano may, in cases where assessments have demonstrated that direct marketing is the most effective manner, follow email and other forms of marketing to promote its business. In such cases this processing will be solely restricted to the processing of Business-to-Business (B2B) contacts. Fiorano will not use direct marketing with non-B2B contacts.
Balancing test: Fiorano will only use direct marketing for occasional business-to-business marketing, to business personnel with decision making / influencing / budgetary responsibilities in a business context who we believe in their roles will reasonably expect to be contacted with marketing material relating to his / her professional role.
In all cases, while we do not anticipate any of our direct marketing to be objectionable, recipients will always have the option to unsubscribe from updates in which case once such communication has been received, Fiorano will move related records to a restricted Do Not Contact database. In no manner and at any point will Fiorano engage in direct marketing activities that does not comply with the Purpose, Necessity and Balancing purposes outlined above, or will Fiorano engage in processing activities that we believe may override the rights of Data Subjects. We also do not sell your information to any other parties.
Your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation:
Under the EUs GDPR laws, you have the following general rights as a data subject:
Access:
the right to request information about how we process your Personal Information and also to obtain a copy of that Personal Information.
Rectification:
the right to request the rectification of inaccurate Personal Information about you and for any incomplete Personal Information about you to be completed.
Objection:
the right to object to the processing of your Personal Information, which is based on our legitimate interests (as described above).
Erasure: the right to request the erasure of your Personal Information (subject to certain conditions).
Automated decision-making:
the right not to have a decision made about you that is based solely on automated processing
Restriction:
the right to ask us to restrict our processing of your Personal Information.
Portability: the right to receive your Personal Information as per our records in a machine readable format free of charge. You may direct us to provide this data to a third party which we will do as is technologically reasonable.
In addition to the above, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your Personal Information infringes applicable data protection law.
Please feel free to direct any questions, comments, or complaints regarding this privacy statement or the privacy practices of Fiorano Software to our Data Protection Officer:
Fiorano Software Limited
Attention: Data Protection Officer
3000 Hillswood Drive, Hillswood Business Park
Chertsey, Surrey KT16 0RS
Phone : +44 (0) 1932895005
Email: privacy@fiorano.com
Post Applied For -
×
Name:
Position:
Previous Experience:
Select
0-1 Years
1-2 Years
2-3 Years
3-4 Years
4-5 Years
Above 5 Years
Previous Company:
Email:
Phone Number:
Cover Letter:
Thank you for your interest. our team will contact shortly.
Error occur in your request, Please try later!.
Close
Submit
×
Contact Us
Submit this form selecting the appropriate message category and the relevant team will get in touch with you shortly.
Name *
Email *
Company *
Phone Number *
Your country or region *
-- Select Country --
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntiguaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanAzoresBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamVirgin IslandsBulgariaBurkina FasoBurmaBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDemocratic Republic of the CongoDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFaroe IslandsFiji IslandsFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNakhodkaNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNiger RepublicNigeriaNiueNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRepublic of the CongoRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre And MiquelonSaint Vincent And The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome And PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbia and MontenegroSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSt. VincentSudanSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTongaTokelauTonga IslandsTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUSAUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaWestern SamoaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe
Which best describes you? *
Select one
Existing Fiorano customer
Senior Management (CEO/CIO/CTO/VP)
Thank you for your interest in Fiorano. Our Fiorano representative will contact you shortly.
Error occur in your request, Please try later!.
We ask for the above Personal information so that we may fulfill your request.
The requested resource will be mailed to the provided email id shortly.
Our team may contact you to confirm receipt of this resource.
To view our complete Privacy policy or how we manage your information, please click here.
I agree to being contacted by Fiorano Software*
* By agreeing, I understand that personal information provided above will be stored by Fiorano to provide the
resources requested and Fiorano may continue to send related information to
you or contact you regarding your request. You can change your preference at
any time by clicking on the Unsubscribe or Change my preferences button provided
at the bottom of the email or by contacting privacy@fiorano.com.
Fiorano may also combine this information with other information
from LinkedIn or other such platforms to send you relevant content
to you based on the organisation you work for.
GDPR gives you specific rights. You may view these in the
Privacy Policy.
Thank you for your interest. The link will be mailed to you shortly.
Error occur in your request, Please try later!.
Get our Fiorano experts to get in touch with you.
Error! Please Enter Your Email Address.
Please provide your Corporate Email Id.
Error! Please Enter Your Email Address.
Please provide your Corporate Email Id.
Follow Us
© 2019 Fiorano Software and Affiliates. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Statement
|
Terms of Use
© 2020 Fiorano Software and Affiliates. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Statement
| Terms of Use
